[Music]
hi
my name is kaziangera puri i'm from
prudential
i've closed 12 cases and i've been with
prudential for a month
every day when i wake up i go out there
looking for the 95 percent of people
[Music]
the money in prudential motivates me
my strategy is that i prospect on the
phone
meet up my clients each and every day
and i go to different
companies different offices
to meet up new people and from there i
get
prospects and that keeps my business
going each and every day
[Music]
so what motivates me the cash the
mullah and
also did you know that only five percent
of the people in zambia know about
insurance
so the 95 percent out there the people
that
i follow each and every day and it's
like
i'm going to just choose maybe a pool
out there where i just need to go and
pick up
clients so that's where i get my
motivation from
by the end of the year i want to close
200 cases
which will help me get to my financial
target of the year
and i'm so confident about it because
there's a lot of business out there
my encouragement to everyone who wants
to join the prudential family is that
you need to believe in yourself
you need to love your job be proud of
what you do let
everybody know what your job is all
about and in that way
you get prospects from all around you
and at the end of the day it's you that
is going to benefit